<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <RB_Organic_Honeycomb.label>organic honeycomb</RB_Organic_Honeycomb.label>
  <RB_Organic_Honeycomb.description>This is a honeycomb produced by organic bees. Organic bees are genetically modified bees that extract cellulose fibers from nearby plants and convert it into a slurry of genetic material which can be refined into template genomes. The main use of these bees, however, is to hybridize them with other bees to create genetic bees of different subspecies. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get honey, beeswax and template genomes.</RB_Organic_Honeycomb.description>

  <RB_Cattle_Honeycomb.label>cattle honeycomb</RB_Cattle_Honeycomb.label>
  <RB_Cattle_Honeycomb.description>This is a honeycomb produced by cattle bees. Cattle bees have muffalo genes spliced in their genome. They are covered in a thick white pelt, and produce milk, wool and muffalo genetic material. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get milk, wool and muffalo genetic material.</RB_Cattle_Honeycomb.description>

  <RB_Clucking_Honeycomb.label>clucking honeycomb</RB_Clucking_Honeycomb.label>
  <RB_Clucking_Honeycomb.description>This is a honeycomb produced by clucking bees. Clucking bees have chicken genes spliced in their genome. They are covered in feathers, and produce eggs and avian genetic material. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get bee eggs, genewax and avian genetic material.</RB_Clucking_Honeycomb.description>

  <RB_Exploding_Honeycomb.label>exploding honeycomb</RB_Exploding_Honeycomb.label>
  <RB_Exploding_Honeycomb.description>This is a honeycomb produced by exploding bees. Exploding bees have boomalope genes spliced in their genome. This bees produce genetic honey, chemfuel, and boom genetic material. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get genetic honey, chemfuel, and booma genetic material.</RB_Exploding_Honeycomb.description>

  <RB_Horned_Honeycomb.label>horned honeycomb</RB_Horned_Honeycomb.label>
  <RB_Horned_Honeycomb.description>This is a honeycomb produced by horned bees. Horned bees have thrumbo genes spliced in their genome. They take a very long time to generate honeycombs, but they produce highly sought after colossal genetic material. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get genetic honey, genewax, and colossal genetic material.</RB_Horned_Honeycomb.description>

  <RB_Hound_Honeycomb.label>hound honeycomb</RB_Hound_Honeycomb.label>
  <RB_Hound_Honeycomb.description>This is a honeycomb produced by hound bees. Hound bees have wolf genes spliced in their genome. They produce canine genetic material. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get genetic honey, genewax and canine genetic material.</RB_Hound_Honeycomb.description>

  <RB_Hybernating_Honeycomb.label>hybernating honeycomb</RB_Hybernating_Honeycomb.label>
  <RB_Hybernating_Honeycomb.description>This is a honeycomb produced by hybernating bees. Hybernating bees have grizzly bear genes spliced in their genome. They are covered in a soft fur. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get genetic honey, genewax and bear genetic material.</RB_Hybernating_Honeycomb.description>


  <!-- <ThingDef ParentName="RB_CombBase">
		<defName>RB_Mecha_Honeycomb</defName>
		<label>mecha honeycomb</label>
		<description>This is a honeycomb produced by mecha bees. These are bee sized mechanoids, apparently under the colonists' control. Mecha bees produce mechanoid active components, which are used to create mechanoid hybrids, but they take a very long time to do so. They'll need a stockpile with a Advanced Components nearby to start refining the mechanites. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get genetic honey, genewax and mechanoid active components.</description>
		<graphicData>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<texPath>Things/Item/Combs/RB_Mecha_Honeycomb</texPath>
		</graphicData>	
		<butcherProducts>
			<RB_GeneticHoney>50</RB_GeneticHoney>
			<RB_Genewax>50</RB_Genewax>
			<GR_MechanoidGenetic>1</GR_MechanoidGenetic>
		</butcherProducts>
	</ThingDef> -->

  <RB_Megaspidery_Honeycomb.label>megaspidery honeycomb</RB_Megaspidery_Honeycomb.label>
  <RB_Megaspidery_Honeycomb.description>This is a honeycomb produced by megaspidery bees. Megaspidery bees have insectoid genes spliced in their genome. They are covered in chitinous plates and produce insect jelly and insectoid genetic materials. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get insect jelly, genewax and insectoid genetic material.</RB_Megaspidery_Honeycomb.description>

  <RB_Mousy_Honeycomb.label>mousy honeycomb</RB_Mousy_Honeycomb.label>
  <RB_Mousy_Honeycomb.description>This is a honeycomb produced by mousy bees. Mousy bees have rodent genes spliced in their genome. They produce rodent genetic materials and many find their constant high-pitched squeaking sounds to be quite distracting. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get genetic honey, genewax and rodent genetic material.</RB_Mousy_Honeycomb.description>

  <RB_Purring_Honeycomb.label>purring honeycomb</RB_Purring_Honeycomb.label>
  <RB_Purring_Honeycomb.description>This is a honeycomb produced by purring bees. Purring bees have cat genes spliced in their genome. They produce feline genetic materials and a lot of videos on the internet. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get genetic honey, genewax and feline genetic material.</RB_Purring_Honeycomb.description>

  <RB_Scaly_Honeycomb.label>scaly honeycomb</RB_Scaly_Honeycomb.label>
  <RB_Scaly_Honeycomb.description>TScaly bees have reptile genes spliced in their genome. They are covered in tough looking scales and produce reptilian genetic materials. Honeycombs can be procesed in a Honey Extractor to get genetic honey, genewax and reptile genetic material.</RB_Scaly_Honeycomb.description>


</LanguageData>