<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <GR_BiomechanicalLabBeacon.label>机械生物实验基地信标</GR_BiomechanicalLabBeacon.label>
  <GR_BiomechanicalLabBeacon.description>内部似乎由精密计算机芯片组成的神秘星形八面体装置。能够自主供电独立运行，核心部分也不知为何会持续发出“嘟嘟嘟”的奇怪响声。将其传输的无线电信号破译后可探明一个机械生物实验基地的位置，但要小心因功率过载而引起的自爆。</GR_BiomechanicalLabBeacon.description>
  <GR_BiomechanicalLabBeacon_Blueprint.label>biomechanical lab beacon (blueprint)</GR_BiomechanicalLabBeacon_Blueprint.label>
  <GR_BiomechanicalLabBeacon_Frame.label>biomechanical lab beacon (building)</GR_BiomechanicalLabBeacon_Frame.label>
  <GR_BiomechanicalLabBeacon_Frame.description>This strange stellated octahedron seems to house an assembly of complex computer chips. It appears to be self-powered, and a faint beeping noise emanates from its core. The radio waves it is constantly emitting are being decoded, but the process seems to have destabilized its power source, and it will blow up soon!</GR_BiomechanicalLabBeacon_Frame.description>

  <GR_MechahybridAntenna.label>机械生物信号塔</GR_MechahybridAntenna.label>
  <GR_MechahybridAntenna.description>用于控制机械生物的大型信号塔。若没有这台设备的帮助，机械生物体内的自我复制型纳米机械将无法及时认证友方单位和更新同步敌我识别系统。\n\n&lt;color=#E5E54C&gt;游戏效果：&lt;/color&gt;未处于信号塔控制下的机械生物将会在一段时间后陷入猎杀人类状态。一个信号塔最多只能控制五个任意体型的机械生物。由于信号的传播距离很远，附近废弃定居点和遗迹中的狂暴机械生物很可能会被吸引过来，并在彷徨畸兽袭击中出现。</GR_MechahybridAntenna.description>
  <GR_MechahybridAntenna_Blueprint.label>mechahybrid antenna (blueprint)</GR_MechahybridAntenna_Blueprint.label>
  <GR_MechahybridAntenna_Frame.label>mechahybrid antenna (building)</GR_MechahybridAntenna_Frame.label>
  <GR_MechahybridAntenna_Frame.description>A large broadcasting server that is specifically tuned to maintain the tameness of mechahybrids. Without this server, the self-replicating mechanites within the mechahybrids will eventually no longer be able to register friendlies as their IFF updates and branches, causing them to go manhunter.\n\n&lt;color=#E5E54C&gt;Gameplay effect:&lt;/color&gt; It is important to note that a single antenna can only broadcast to a limited number of mechahybrids, specifically up to 5 of them regardless of their size or complexity. Any additionally mechahybrid present beyond the initial 5 will no longer receive updates and will eventually lose their "tameness". Part of the broadcast will reach nearby settlements and ruins, attracting maddened mechahybrids, so they will appear from the moment you have a mechahybrid antenna in the periodic roaming monstrosities raids.</GR_MechahybridAntenna_Frame.description>

  <GR_Mechahybridizer.label>机械生物改造厂</GR_Mechahybridizer.label>
  <GR_Mechahybridizer.description>通过对无瑕生物注入定量纳米机械以进行改造的大型装置。因为所有工序都是在可控模式下进行的，所以完全不会出现排异反应等可能会导致失败的情况。一旦需要接受改造的无瑕生物就位完毕，改造厂就会自动将内部封闭起来，并向星球轨道上距离最近的机械族巢穴发送回收信号。\n\n这种装置原本是建立在动物世界上的机械族自动装配设施的一部分，其主要用途便是对当地动物进行大量武器化改造，以此来扩充机械族的部队。由于纳米机械的侵袭性很强，为了避免实验体暴毙和材料遭到浪费，接受改造的生物必须选用那些基因完美无缺的“无瑕”个体才行。然而天然的“无瑕”个体实在太过稀少，这种装置最终被安放在了机械族现有的基因工程设施里，并通过定期从外部召唤回收巡逻队来处理产生的废弃材料。\n\n&lt;color=#E5E54C&gt;游戏效果：&lt;/color&gt;如果在缺少保险装置的情况下进行改造，一支负责回收的机械族巡逻队将会在6小时后被空投至此处。</GR_Mechahybridizer.description>

  <GR_Mechafuse.label>改造保险装置</GR_Mechafuse.label>
  <GR_Mechafuse.description>从设计理念与技术含量来看，这台装置并非出自机械族之手。为了阻止机械生物改造厂向机械族巢穴发送回收信号，其制造者通过效仿机械生物改造厂内部系统的方式研发了它。\n\n改造保险装置可以拦截机械生物改造厂发送的回收信号。一旦拦截成功，保险装置将通过自毁来欺骗改造厂的内部系统，使其认为信号发送成功且回收巡逻队已经抵达。\n\n&lt;color=#E5E54C&gt;游戏效果：&lt;/color&gt;如果在缺少保险装置的情况下进行改造，一支负责回收的机械族巡逻队将会在6小时后被空投至此处。</GR_Mechafuse.description>


</LanguageData>